MALIKA EFREMOVA

+995 593 95 17 33 malikaefremova@gmail.com

FRONTEND DEVELOPER / GRAPHIC DESIGNER





Frontend developer passionate about coding and my profession. Capable of quickly learning new programming languages and obtaining new skills.

Already having a few frontend languages, libraries and frameworks such as HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery and React JS on my tech skills list, these days I am slowly moving to the backend programming by learning Node.js, Express.js and Mongo DB. Past experience with PHP and MySQL is a great asset during this enthusiastic journey!

EXPERIENCE

10/2020 – present FREELANCE FRONTEND DEVELOPER

05/2017 – 04/2020 **VIVO MEDICAL LTD** (2 HR employees per 1000+ staff)

HR administrative specialist

02/2013 – 03/2017 INTERPRINTGEORGIA LTD + KOKENI LTD

Graphic designer

10/2007 – 04/2014 **ARADANI LTD**

Graphic designer

09/2007 – 05/2011 ILIA STATE UNIVERSITY

Graphic design & digital media teacher (part-time)

EDUCATION

TBILISI STATE ACADEMY OF ARTS Graphic design & digital media

SKILLS

HTML, CSS JavaScript Node.js, Express.js MongoDB, Mongoose

Bootstrap, Sass, SCSS React JS, jQuery PHP MySQL

Mocha.js, Chai.js Git, GitHub C++

Photoshop Illustrator, CorelDRAW InDesign MS Office

LANGUAGES

NativeC2C1A2A1GeorgianRussianEnglishFrenchJapanese

Lithuanian German

INTERESTS

Linguistics Coding Photography Drawing Travelling Medicine